broadcast knife sales assistant funny videos of deadly crash landing San Francisco in Sunnyvale what was happening in the car
致命的崩溃降落旧金山桑尼维尔发生了什么事在车上的广播刀销售助理搞笑视频
save tonight about what math is falling in the ocean International Space Station American boy
今晚保存有关数学正在下降在海洋国际空间站的美国男孩
hail Jesus you're my whole family is sick temperatures for days whats a good price for safe same line
冰雹耶稣你是我的整个家庭会生病温度天什么好价钱的安全线相同
and no more shot for allergy sufferers new alternative no noodles involve the doctor
和过敏没有更多的出手病友新的替代无面涉及医生
headquarters in New York NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
总部设在纽约的NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
dreaming I'm in Carrizo Bryant
做梦我在卡里佐科比
Bill Maher making a long trip back tonight reporting in South Africa and we begin with starting to tails when out hearing for the first time
比尔马哈尔做一次长途旅行回来，今晚在南非的报告，我们首先开始尾巴出来时，听证会在第一时间
about what may have contributed to a plane crash in San Francisco last a life
什么可能导致了飞机坠毁在旧金山最后一个生命贡献
3 people died 180 were injured in now expert witnesses say it made an example of a pilot online to watch on computers is what they call Automation addiction and Costello has been following the store closely now joint with tails tonight I'm grieving
3人死亡180人受伤现在专家证人说，它做了一个试验的例子在线观看电脑上的是他们所谓的自动化成瘾和科斯特洛一直关注这家店现在紧密联合尾巴今晚我悲伤
hi and good evening this was a better an Airbus pilot app controls of a Boeing triple 7 he may not understood with a superior also in the cockpit they didn't realize they were flying 40 miles per hour to slow and didn't a continental drift seconds before the crash when it was too late
喜晚上好，这是一个更好的空客飞行员应用程序中的波音三联7的他可能不理解上级还在驾驶舱他们没意识到他们是驾驶每小时40英里的速度下降，并没有一个大陆漂移控制时为时已晚在飞机坠毁前秒
from the in TSP new surveillance video showing flight 214 crashing into the sea wall astral I am finally cartulina round and slamming on the runway at SFO
从在TSP中新的监控录像显示飞行214撞向海堤星体我终于cartulina团团地一声在跑道在证券及期货条例
we offer condolences to those who lost love ones
我们慰问那些谁失去了所爱的人
today investigators laid out of fatal cockpit combination before the crash pilots feeling to notice the airspeed was too low compute the plains automated systems work even Korean cultural sensitivity one big focus the automated systems on the Boeing triple 7
今天调查奠定了致命的驾驶舱组合前坠毁飞行员感觉注意到空速过低计算平原自动化系统工作，即使韩国文化敏感性的一大重点波音自动化系统三7
the training Pilots still maintain his speed even though he switched off auto pilot a land manually
训练飞行员依然保持他的速度，即使他手动关闭自动驾驶土地
he was a very experience pilot
他是个非常体验试点
the Korean pilots union suggested a design flaw compute the crew what bowling in sisters system is widely used and flying the plane is up to the pilot not the computer the pilot
朝鲜飞行员工会提出了一个设计缺陷计算什么保龄球姐妹系统广泛应用于船员和飞行的飞机是由飞行员没有电脑试点
final authority for the operation of the airplane we would try not to put in design elements taking over eyes of pilot
最终的权威飞机的操作，我们会尽量不要放接管眼睛试点的设计元素
Licon cook was the printing pilot was flying on his final triple 7 checkout flight with the training captain
力诚厨师是印刷飞行员飞行在他的最后三7结帐飞行与训练队长
he told NTSB investigators he was cold very concerned about lending manually because the airports automated glide slope with Skype outlets in without service
他告诉NTSB调查人员，他是冷的很关心放贷手动，因为机场的自动下滑道与Skype网点没有服务
he feel too much for separate warnings for my copilot that he was descending to rapidly and he said with his superiors watching his Loma position would make it very hard to abort a landing on go around veteran pilots say there's a lesson in relying to have a lien automation
他觉得太为我的副驾驶单独的警告，他被降迅速，他与他的上司看他洛马地位将使它很难中止降落在四处老牌飞行员说有依托有留置权的教训说：自动化
you have to keep up with basic German ship in order to make the other systems
你必须跟上基本德国船，以使其他系统
on behalf of Safety instead of work again safety
代表安全，而不是再工作安全
last month code for much more simulator time for us pilots to be f***** manual flying skills training brought me into the cell
上个月代码更加模拟器的时间让我们的飞行员为f *****手动飞行技能培训领我到小区
it's imperative the files get to practice this is the first time in a simulator ever getting a haircut
它必须将文件一定要把这是第一次在模拟器曾经去理发
11 PSP focus today on whether the pilot is Jana are taught how Boleyn's automated systems working weather privately was confused by the differences between the Boeing and Airbus systems ane
11 PSP今日重点关注是否飞行员亚娜被教导如何博林的自动化系统气象工作私下里感到困惑的波音和空客系统之间的差异ANE
sore on your part time in time Lake this afternoon heard about an urgent situation where the International Space Station at this moment what do we know
疼你的一部分时间在湖时间今天下午听说了紧急情况下的国际空间站在这一刻我们知道什么
NASA telling NBCNews a situation has developed on the orbiting space station Distortion but not an emergency still at Mary choir a spacewalk
美国航空航天局说NBCNews的情况已经在玛丽开发的轨道空间站失真但不紧急仍然合唱团太空行走
within the next one or two weeks to do a repair earlier today 12 cooling systems on the space station stop working engineers believe there is a problem with a flow control valve trim of non essential equipment on the station on route in critical systems to another cooling loop
接下来的一两个星期今天早些时候做修复中的空间站站12冷却系统工作的工程师认为有一个与非必要的设备到另一个冷却回路线路上的站关键系统的流量控制阀内件有问题
so far all external electrical equipment seems to be working just fine the question is whether they can fix this with a software patch or whether they will impact need a spacewalk onboard right now 3 Russians
到目前为止，所有的外部电气设备似乎工作得很好，问题是他们是否能够解决这个问题有一个软件补丁或是否会影响需要一个太空行走板载现在3俄罗斯
Americans 1 Japanese astronaut space walk so not allowed Santana talian astronaut helmet filled with water during a spacewalk in July the ISS by the waist but the size of a football stadium when a million pounds say hope to get it cooled down dramatically is soon as I can
美国1日本宇航员太空行走所以不准在七月在国际空间站进行太空行走期间，桑塔纳talian宇航员头盔装满水的腰，但一个足球场的大小，当万英镑说希望得到它冷却下来大大是只要我能
alright sounds for dramatic a right thank you so much time Costello tonight about those reports Rustler new tail tonight about the family including for children rescued in good shape
戏剧性的权利好吗声音，谢谢你这么多时间科斯特洛今晚那些报道鲁斯特勒新尾今晚对家庭，包括儿童获救状况良好
after spending tonight in subzero temperatures in the mountains of Nevada NBC's Miguel Almaguer has made his way to the scene and has a report
今晚在零度以下的温度在内华达州NBC的米格尔Almaguer山上度过后一路走来现场，有一个报告
from this Lovelock Nevada hospital comes a story of survival with wind up the miracle in the mountains the six survivors on speaking tonight what the doctor who treated them
从这个洛夫洛克内华达州医院来生存的故事，风在山上的奇迹在今晚说什么谁对待他们的医生六个幸存者
the snow is started playing at the Hilton this is like a slow motion
雪开始打在希尔顿这就像一个慢动作
on our journey to retrace stair steps we take you to the rugged and remote hi desert this is where James Glanton Christina mcIntee and 4 children ages 3 through 10 spent tonight trapped in -20 degree weather
在我们的旅程，追溯我们带你到崎岖和偏远沙漠喜楼梯台阶这就是詹姆斯Glanton克里斯蒂娜mcIntee和4个孩子3岁到10度过今晚被困在-20度的天气
where are the off road for about 45 minutes or 30 miles outside of town this is where you can see the footprints in the snow in the hell here overturned Jeep amazing anybody could even survives crash
在哪里越野的城外约45分钟或30英里，在这里你可以看到脚印在地狱里的雪在这里朝天吉普惊人的人甚至可以生存崩溃
we found a jeep still leaking gas smell enough fuel
我们发现了一辆吉普车继续泄漏煤气味足够的燃料
the family was dress for the snow but they are prepared another way to say have bottles of water we found a machete
家庭是礼服的雪，但他们准备另一种说法已经瓶水，我们发现了一个砍刀
flashlight and they use the interior of a jeep here for shelter at night
手电筒和他们用一辆吉普车的内部在这里借宿在夜间
searchteen say James Glanton kept his family alive by keeping them together and staying with the vehicle
sea​​rchteen说詹姆斯Glanton保持他的家人还活着保持它们放在一起，留与车辆
jaded one hell of a job keeping kids safe for a lot of people have been able to do that for two days in subzero temperatures
工作保持孩子们的安全了很多人的疲惫地狱已经能够做到这两天在零度以下的温度
the family gathering sagebrush an even break the spare tire down to the bone to keep warm we're also told a heat up rocks like this one and put them inside the vehicle at night to keep kids warm
家庭聚会山艾树的甚至下降打破了备胎的骨保暖我们还讲了一个热起来的岩石像这样的，把他们的车内，晚上让孩子们温暖
dehydration in a statement the family act for privacy taking search and rescue teams for their dedication a happy ending Utah State ever see Miguel Almaguer NBC News Lovelock Nevada
脱水在一份声明中家庭行为的隐私服用搜索和救援队为他们的奉献精神大团圆结局犹他州州立见过米格尔Almaguer NBC新闻内华达州拉夫洛克
end of the nation's capital budget deal with told you about last night while the agreement avoid another government shutdown next month it also sidestep dealing with the crisis facing 1.3 million Americans out of work for a long time
国家的资本预算处理结束告诉你，昨晚虽然该协议避免另一个政府关闭下个月也回避应对面临130万美国人失去工作很长一段时间的危机
and that means there unemployment benefits will stop at the end of the month unless Congress takes action is Joe friar talk to some of the families were worried about what comes next
这意味着有失业救济金将停止在月底，除非国会采取行动，是乔修士聊到一些家属担心下一步怎么走
flu shot Daniels Palmer a mother of 4 much for morning ritual remains the same getting your kids up and ready for school but these day she supporting her family with her unemployment insurance
流感预防针丹尼尔斯帕尔默4多的晨礼的母亲依旧让您的孩子并准备上学，但这些天她支持她的家人和她的失业保险
Anne at 375 week it's really tough is really really talk
安妮在375本周，真的很难是真的真的谈
what's your computer now broken tree hunt for work on her tiny cell phone screen this is week 28 of unemployment account every week because that number is never counted more for benefits could sue disappear
什么是你的电脑现在坏树追捕她小小的手机屏幕上的工作，这是失业的帐户28周每星期，因为这个数字的好处绝对算的更多的可以起诉消失
I need the benefit so that I can keep pushin forward so that I want me the benefits
我需要的利益，这样我可以保持推着向前，让我要我的好处
up until 2009 unemployment benefits last 26 weeks but today because of the recession they can go up to 73 weeks but if Congress doesn't take action Bail go back to 26 weeks on December 28 in 1.3 million jobless workers will lose their benefits
最多到2009年失业救济金过去26个星期，但今天由于经济衰退，他们可以去到73个星期，但如果国会不采取行动保释回到26周12月28日的130万失业工人将失去他们的福利
set include Randi Rousseau who did Spike Lee ving in Chicago keeps the heat low to save money
一套包括兰迪卢梭谁做了斯派克·李咏在芝加哥保持低热量省钱
I don't know what the end game is to win it would happen if its the fattest hope you don't have a hope that it's truly over
我不知道到底是什么游戏来赢得它会发生，如果它的最胖的，希望你不要有一个希望，它的真正结束
what what appointment is gradually improve job fairs like this continue to draw clouds people who say they need benefits for work economist charge you a longer stretches benefits cost taxpayers billions discourage people from looking hard for jobs
什么什么约会逐步完善招聘会像这样继续画云谁的人说，他们需要工作的经济学家费的好处你一个较长的延绵福利花费纳税人数十亿阻碍人们定神求职
unemployed people buy Mauna play for longer time as a consequence of the program
失业的人买的Mauna玩更长的时间，因为该计划的结果
LaShawn Daniels Palmer say she's willing to take almost any job
LaShawn丹尼尔斯帕尔默说她愿意接受几乎任何工作
I'm not be on working in retail store I'm not be on working at McDonalds whatever it takes at my kids and I homeless
我不会在零售商店工作，我不能在麦当劳工作不惜一切代价在我的孩子，我无家可归
she's not counting the weeks and Teller benefits and Joe fryer NBC News Los Angeles
她不算周和Teller利益和乔油炸NBC新闻洛杉矶
Ameris news about President healthcare law find apps on both the federal and state exchanges are improving but not fast enough to meet in Roman goals in ministration for stealing 365
Ameris新闻关于对联邦和各州的交流既总统的医疗保健法律的发现应用程序正在改善，但速度还不够快在服侍罗马的目标，以满足偷365
that is 3 times more than the October numbers what's so far short of the goal of 1.2 million through the end of November
比十月份的数字的3倍以上什么是至今短短的120万的目标，到11月底
and problems with healthcare law are having a big impact on the president's approval ratings according to our new NBC News Wall Street Journal poll little director in chief White House correspondent on tonight with more explained
和问题的医疗保健法是有根据我们新的NBC新闻华尔街日报民调中很少首席白宫记者，今晚上有更多的导演对总统的支持率有很大的影响解释
what is a weight on the President you know when you look at approval rating is sitting at 43 percent approval that's near his all time low on that number disapproval rating of the 54 percent ethanol time I've never been high and it is clearly healthcare which is the prison
什么是对总统的重量，当你在支持率你知道是坐在43％的支持那是靠近他的所有时间低的54％的乙醇时候，我从来没有去过高，这个数字不满意的比率，这显然是医疗保健的是监狱
what the public is viewing the president of all the issues in a bunch of top 16 2013 from the shutdown the economy all these things and it is healthcare 58 percent that is seen as the driver of how the public is shaking their opinion of this president
什么是公众从关机经济所有这些事情看在了一堆顶部16 2013年所有问题的总裁，这是医疗保健被视为公众是如何晃动这位总统的他们认为司机58％
look at the health care law now is more popular than ever good idea bad idea with a tracking device for 3 years for the first time
看卫生保健法是现在比为3年一个跟踪装置的第一次好主意坏主意更受欢迎
ama Jordan say its a bad idea but there's a glimmer of hope if you're the White House and the fact that only 26 percent basically 14 Merrick bank velocity scrap all together there's a much larger majority I would like to see effects of the White House phone number to realize
AMA乔丹说，它是一个坏主意，但有一丝希望，如果你是白宫和事实，即只有26％，基本上14梅里克银行速度废料一起有一个更大的大部分我想看看白宫的影响电话号码来实现
not good news but you do a public according are poster who would like to see the law work at the White House clean up the political problems to make it work
不是一个好消息，但你的公开按照海报是谁希望看到在白宫法律工作清理的政治问题，使其工作
thank you for the perspective that you were you pull a given time and date now the temperature Asians in Ukraine
谢谢你，你是你拉一个给定的时间和日期现在的角度来看，温度亚洲人在乌克兰
stration of an escalating for weeks
不断升级的几个星期的习作
protesters 130 in left aligned with Russia enter calling for closer ties with Europe
示威者在左与俄罗斯对齐130输入要求与欧洲更紧密的联系
Ukraine president has pulled his wife leaseback for now but the protester say they won't sit down with him for talk to the release of those interested
乌克兰总统把他的妻子回租的，但现在的抗议者说，他们不会坐下来和他聊到那些有兴趣的释放
fires is government
火灾是政府
still have tonight Dr Nancy Snyderman with welcome news for millions of Americans of allergy shots get the shot there is now a new alternative no needles
还有今晚南希斯奈德曼与数以百万计的美国人过敏射击的好消息得到医生的射门，现在有一个新的选择没有针
Hill and later lost in translation how many people were affected by the sign language on stage
希尔后来在翻译中丢失多少人受到影响，在台上的手语
we're back now and our health news tonight is about allergies one of the most common elements in the United States 15 Americans has reactions to Paul in Dauphin other things we breathe in and two and a half million get allergy shots are the monthly or weekly
我们回到现在，我们的健康新闻，今晚是关于过敏的，在美国15美国人最常见的元素之一在我们呼吸的两个多芬其他的东西，反应保罗五十万得到过敏射击是在每月或每周
now there's an alternative being considered for approval no noodles just a pillow under your tongue to report a remark chief medical editor Dr Nancy Snyder
现在有正在审核的替代没有面条在你的舌头只是一个枕头来报告了一句话首席医学编辑南茜·斯奈德博士
breakfast Morningside Louise Angeles house are always busy
早餐晨路易丝洛杉矶的房子总是很忙
getting 7 year old college ready for school
让7岁的大学准备上学
feeding a dog Sophia and packing emergency allergy kit Boo's mother and daughter have severe reactions to ragweed grass in tree pollen and animal dander and get frequent allergy shots
饲养一只狗索菲亚和包装应急工具包过敏嘘的母亲和女儿有严重的反应，豚草，草，树木花粉及动物皮屑，并得到频繁的过敏射击
we have runny nose puffy eyes itchy throat coughing dry dry hacking cough and sometimes hives
我们有流鼻涕眼睛浮肿，咽痒咳嗽，燥燥干咳，有时荨麻疹
Louise and cause me to have another option to injections to Dayton FDA Advisory Committee met
路易丝和使我有另一种选择，以注射顿FDA咨询委员会举行会议
approved to respiratory allergy drugs already available in Europe
获准在欧洲已经有呼吸道过敏的药物
daily dose pills to dissolve under the tongue Dr David stoner is an allergy specialist in Allegany health
每日剂量药片含在舌下溶解大卫博士斯托纳在阿勒格尼健康过敏专家
networking tips for good morning Lisa
对于早上好丽莎的联网提示
the two big groups that I see that would really benefit from this at the RV rebus the People
我看到两个大组将真正从中受益的RV画谜人民
the cant fit
该斜面贴合
visit to a doctors office for shot into the busy schedules and those who are Neal ever
参观到医生办公室拍摄到繁忙的日程和那些谁是有史以来尼尔
Dr scooter is also a consulting firm work what is the manufactures the allergy pill under FDA review there's a trade off
博士踏板车也是一家咨询公司工作有什么根据生产FDA审查的过敏丸有一个权衡
the tablets called or later and Graphtec on the cover specific graft Pollins shotgun offer brother protection amor allergens I can be personalized
所谓的片剂或更高版本以及绘图技术封面特定接枝Pollins猎枪报价哥哥保护阿穆尔我的过敏原可以个性化
vigil what we could try to do if I can set the weather pills would be more convenient injections patience my sacrifice a doctor supervision office
守夜我们可以尝试做的，如果我可以设置天气丸会比较方便注射的耐心我的牺牲医生监督办公室
always have to be extremely cautious when patients start taking medication at home since allergen immunotherapy runs the risk of adverse reactions like
总是必须非常谨慎，当患者开始服药在家，因为过敏原免疫疗法运行的不良反应类似的风险
Electric reaction you want to make sure a patient is properly educated about the safest medication and especially how to take
你要确保患者电反应是适当的教育有关的最安全的药物，尤其是如何利用
thank you so much tonight and 1 word help no tonight the Food and Drug Administration is taking new steps to phase out the use of antibiotics in meat
非常感谢你今晚和1个字帮助没有今晚的食品和药物管理局正采取新的措施，逐步淘汰在肉类中的抗生素
the FDA is asking pharmaceutical companies to voluntarily stop marketing does drugs for use in animal feed this is meant reduce the number of antibiotic resistance
FDA正在要求制药公司自愿停止销售确实药物在动物饲料中使用，这是意味着减少抗生素耐药性的数
is is in humans upNext what happens when Presidents their wives and Hillary Clinton travel together on the same flight
是是人类upNext总统时，他们的妻子和希拉里一起旅行在同一个航班会发生什么
to 9000 South Africans are lining up to you Nelson Mandela slide break ask if you live in state in South Africa's capital Victoria inside the same as a theater when he was sworn in as president almost 20 years ago
9000南非正在排队给你曼德拉滑断裂问，如果你住在状态在南非首都维多利亚里面一样的剧院时，他宣誓就任总统近20年前
MLB 2 more days a public viewing for Mandela is laid to rest on Sunday
美国职棒大联盟2多天的公众观看的曼德拉被安葬在周日
and in South Africa tonight controversy over man
而在南非今晚争论的人
did next President Obama at on the podium at Mandela memorial sign language interpreter summon the deaf community are saying he's a fake is gestures work sign language at all NPCs Ron Allen has been looking into the store and imports mail from South Africa
做下一任总统奥巴马在上在曼德拉纪念手语翻译召唤聋人社区讲台是说他是一个假的手势工作用手语在所有的NPC罗恩 - 阿伦已经寻找到了商店，进口邮件来自南非
was there an even when President Obama spoke today outrage from death and hearing impaired South Africans say the so-called interpreter what's the complete fraud
在那里的，即使奥巴马总统今天从死亡说话的愤怒和听力受损的南非人说的所谓解释器有什么完整的欺诈行为
Bay cities to watch 38 offset and so is zero
湾城观看38抵消，所以是零
she said the only sin she saw ironically what's the word help
她说，她看到具有讽刺意味的​​是什么字帮助的唯一罪过
television
电视
the difference with a parent
与父母的区别
angry Joe Twitter
愤怒的Twitter的乔
no idea
不知道
Jacob Zuma
雅各布·祖马
professionals with any known sin
与任何已知的罪专业人员
the government really hard the interpreter for Mandela service dealing with Arrangements Dallas funeral today even the White House weight in
政府真的很难解释为曼德拉今天的服务处理安排达拉斯葬礼甚至白宫重量
baby Seamus a distraction about the individuals on stage anyway to track it from the important event in the importance of President of the sea
宝宝西莫一个关于舞台上的人分心反正从海上总统的重要性重要事件跟踪它
David Boston of the British do to interpretation he is making
英国的大卫·波士顿做解释，他正在
there is no sense toy is doing icon CNE meaning to what he's doing
是没有意义的玩具做图标CNE意义他在做什么
history modern translation
历史今译
the whole world's watching
全世界的注视
victorious
胜
and one more night on the president of South Africa this week summer markable images from inside Air Force One
和南非总统这个星期的夏季印刷用图片从里面空军一号一晚
Mr Obama and former President George W Bush travel to South Africa long with their wives and former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton and what are the images Mr Bush you enjoy spanking has taken out his iPad not showing Hillary Clinton Michelle Obama some of his work
奥巴马和前总统乔治·W·布什前往南非长期与他们的妻子和前国务卿希拉里·克林顿和什么样的图像布什先生你喜欢打屁股已经采取了他的iPad没有显示希拉里米歇尔·奥巴马他的一些作品
White House photographer pizza to use on a graph
白宫摄影师的比萨饼上的图形用
and when we come back he may lose when he pose for a selfie in St Peters tonight why he's making all over again
而当我们回来，他可能会失去他时的姿势在圣彼得一个selfie今晚他为什么做一遍
as you may have heard Time magazine an ounce Pope Francis as a spit for Person of the Year he's the third Pokemon that honor the first
正如你可能已经听说过时代杂志每盎司教皇弗朗西斯作为一吐为年度人物，他是第三口袋妖怪的荣誉第一
in 19 years times has a chosen because quotes rarely has a new player on the world stage capture so much attention so quickly
19年的时间有一个选择，因为引号很少有在世界舞台上捕捉一个新的球员如此多的关注如此之快
embassies and Thompson who is travels with his new pope reports on the game changer in the Vatican
大使馆和汤普森谁是旅行与上改变游戏规则在他的梵蒂冈新教皇报告